Won’t leave
떠나려면
without a dropkick on her!
저 애에게 드롭킥을 날려야 해
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas
자자스 자자스 나사타나다 자자스
-She summoned me, the evil god. -Evil god!
- 저 애가 소환한 난 악마다 - 악마다!
-I gotta kill her or else -What?
저 애를 죽이지 않으면 뭐?
-I can’t go back to Hell! -Sister...
지옥에 갈 수가 없어 자매여...
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Life next to death, I combat with my chainsaw!
그래! 그래! 그래! 죽음과 살기 위해, 전기톱으로 싸워야지!
If you go too far,
네가 막 나가면
I’ll slice you up completely!
널 완전히 썰어버릴 거야!
Your halo! Must get it back!
네 후광을 반드시 되찾아야지!
-Never miss a chance -Hey, seriously?
기회를 절대 놓치지 마 정말 그럴 거야?
-To attack her from behind! -You’re so mean.
뒤에서 공격하려고? 넌 못됐어
I’ll never give up.
난 절대 포기 안 해
Yurine, you’re off your guard!
유리네, 방심하고 있군!
Now! Time to finish you with the Royal Copenhagen!
지금이다! 로열코펜하겐으로 끝내주지!
Huh? What? I missed...
어, 뭐지? 실패다...
Can’t leave Earth
지구를 떠나려면
without a dropkick on her!
저 애에게 드롭킥을 날려야 해
But until then,
하지만 그때까진
-let’s all have fun together! -Yeah!
모두 같이 놀자! 신난다!
Once a post-World War II black market,
제2차 세계대전 이후 한때 암시장이었고
it has since evolved into an electronics then computer district,
그 이후 전자제품과 컴퓨터 구역으로 진화했습니다
and now flourishes today as the mecca of otaku.
오늘날엔 오타쿠 성지로 성황을 이루는
This is Akihabara.
이곳이 아키하바라입니다
You'll find more than 400 Gachapon machines here.
가차폰 기계가 400대 이상 있는 곳이죠
GACHAPON HALL
'가차폰 회관'
You won't be able to resist the urge to play!
이곳에선 게임 충동을 억누를 수 없죠
If this comes out next, I'll die.
다음에 이게 나오면 난 죽을 거야
My life's spared. But a skyfish? Lame!
내 목숨은 건졌지만 스카이피시야? 한심하군!
But, boy, I can't get enough of that adrenaline rush putting my life on the line!
내 목숨이 걸린 아슬아슬하고 짜릿한 기분을 계속 느끼고 싶다
It's not like I'm really gonna die anyway.
내가 진짜 죽는 것도 아니니까
I don't need any more of you.
너희들은 있으니까 더 필요 없어
What in the--?
이건 뭐...?
You bastard! Can't you see this devil lying in the street?
나쁜 놈! 이 악마님이 길에 누운 게 안 보여?
You might as well drive into a pole and die!
기둥에다 차를 들이박고 죽어라!
Hello, everyone, please do not lie down in the street
안녕하세요, 여러분 거리에 눕지 마세요
and shout obscenities in public.
공공장소에서 욕하고 소리쳐도 안 돼요
Damn it, another double!
제길, 또 둘이군!
Burn in Hell!
지옥으로 꺼져!
I just need that rare Tsuchinoko and my collection's complete.
귀한 쓰치노코만 구하면 내 수집이 완성되는데
Nope. Not interested in the actual, physical one.
아니야, 난 실제 형체엔 관심 없어
We can't have pets in Yurine's apartment.
유리네 아파트에선 애완동물을 못 키워
Beth being an exception, of course.
물론 베스는 예외지
Let's try this again.
다시 한번 해보자
I only have enough to buy dinner.
저녁 살 돈밖에 없네?
But, let's live it up...
하지만, 즐겁게 사는 거야
Don't you dare waste that money.
그 돈을 마구 쓸 건 아니지?
If you do, I'll throw you in the wood chipper.
그랬다간 널 톱밥제조기에 던져 넣는다
Throw you in the woodchipper...
톱밥제조기에 넣는다...
Woodchipper...?
톱밥제조기...?
Woodchippers grind wood into smaller woodchips.
톱밥제조기는 나무를 갈아서 톱밥을 만드는 기계죠
One mistake using it, and you're on your way to hell!
사용 중 조그만 실수라도 하면 곧장 지옥으로 갑니다!
Speak of the devil...
악마라는 말이 나온 김에...
If I spend this money, I'm dead. I give up.
이 돈을 썼다간 죽어 내가 포기한다
Excuse me...
저기요...
-I wanna do that one. -Go ahead.
- 그거 하고 싶어요 - 네가 해
"I wanna do that one."
"그거 하고 싶어요"
"Let's do it."
"같이 하자"
It's a Tsuchinoko!
쓰치노코다!
What?
뭐?
-Damn it! -That completes my collection!
- 제기랄! - 다 모았다!
I tried so many times to get that Tsuchinoko!
난 쓰치노코를 얻으려고 그렇게 많이 했는데
And this kid gets it on his first try?
이 꼬마는 한 번에 저걸 따냈어?
I want it so bad!
정말 갖고 싶어!
That Tsuchinoko looks glorious!
저 쓰치노코는 정말 멋지다!
I'll kill him.
이 애를 죽일 거야
Without so much as a pang of guilt, I'll make that Tsuchinoko mine!
별다른 죄의식 없이 쓰치노코를 내가 가질 수 있어
Wait a minute.
잠깐
There's gotta be a smarter way to get it from him.
저걸 뺏을 더 나은 방법이 있잖아?
For I am an advanced, high-level schemer of a devil.
난 고도로 세련된 계략을 쓸 수 있는 상급 악마지
Wow, that's amazing. You got the rare Tsuchinoko.
정말 멋지다 그 귀한 쓰치노코를 땄어?
Can I get a closer look?
내가 자세히 봐도 될까?
Sure, here you go.
네, 보세요
Here you go.
받아
What the hell was that for?
그게 무슨 짓이야?
Damn snake!
죽어라, 뱀아!
You're disgusting!
더러워!
You're the worst.
넌 정말 못됐어
I don't even want it back, you idiot.
돌려받기도 싫다, 멍청이야
Thanks for the heartfelt compliment, little boy.
진심으로 칭찬해줘서 고맙다, 꼬마
Success!
성공이다!
Got my Tsuchinoko! All right!
쓰치노코를 얻었다! 신난다
Time to shop and head home.
장 봐서 집에 가야지
MEAT PAVILION YUKIO
'육류 코너 유키오'
That was a steal for such good meat.
이렇게 좋은 고기를 아주 싸게 샀다
I even got my Tsuchinoko, I'm on a roll today.
쓰치노코도 얻었으니 오늘은 승운이 따르는군
You're the worst!
넌 정말 못됐어
Now that I think about it...
지금 생각해보니...
was it really worth stealing?
이게 정말 뺏을 가치가 있었나?
Every time I see this,
이걸 볼 때마다
the memory of the boy beating me up will replay in my head.
그 꼬마애가 날 때린 기억이 머리에서 떠오를 거야
I'll store it so I don't see it when I get home.
집에 가면 안 보이게 넣어둬야지
Hey, you!
어이, 당신!
Yeah, I'm talking to you, snake!
그래, 너 말이야 뱀아!
An unknown number. Hello?
모르는 번호네 여보세요?
-Is this Yurine Hanazono? -Yes.
- 하나조노 유리네 씨인가요? - 네
-This is Banzaibashi Police. -Police?
- 반자이바시 경찰입니다 - 경찰요?
-Hey! -Yurine!
- 이봐! - 유리네!
I got arrested by the police!
나 경찰서에 잡혀있어!
They really locked me up.
날 정말 가뒀어
Don't you dare act
별거 아닌 듯이 넘기려는
like you can get away with this!
그런 짓은 하지 마
The second uppercut of the day. Rough.
오늘의 두 번째 어퍼컷이다 세다
No chance for me to explain? You'd be a bad parent!
설명할 기회는 줘야지? 넌 나쁜 부모야
I don't intend to be a parent.
난 부모 노릇 할 생각 없어
Are you Yurine Hanazono, her guardian?
당신이 이 여자 보호자인 하나조노 유리네 씨인가요?
Sure, I guess.
네, 그런 것 같아요
Anyway, who are you?
그런데 당신은 누구죠?
Who am I?
내가 누구냐고요?
I'm the Banzaibashi super cop who keeps the peace in Akiba!
난 아키바의 평화를 지키는 반자이바시 슈퍼 경찰관
Mei Tachibana!
타치바나 메이요!
-Oh, right. -Who do you think you are?
- 그렇군요 - 대단한 줄 아나 봐?
So tell me, what did Jashin-chan do?
사신짱이 무슨 짓을 했는지 말씀해 주세요
She committed theft.
절도죄를 저질렀어요
You gotta be kidding me.
정말 기가 막히는군
You got it all wrong! Hear me out!
잘못 안 거야! 내 말을 들어 봐
I don't even want it back, you idiot!
돌려받기도 싫다, 멍청이야
-What are you talking about? -What do you mean?
- 무슨 말을 하는 거야? - 그게 아니에요?
She stole...
이 애가 훔친 건...
My heart! My heart!
내 마음이야 바로 내 마음!
I found her while on patrol
순찰 중에 이 애를 발견했죠
and she was so beautiful, I fell in love at first sight!
그런데 너무 아름다워서 첫눈에 사랑에 빠졌어요
So, I stopped her and arrested her!
그래서 이 애를 못 가게 막고 체포한 거예요
So cute! So beautiful!
너무 예쁘고 정말 아름다워요!
Get away from me!
저리 가지 못해?
You're just abusing your power!
이건 권력 남용이라고!
-You're just too cute! -Stop!
- 넌 너무 예뻐! - 하지 마!
-Let's get to the real issue here. -Yes?
- 이제 본론으로 들어가죠 - 네?
-May I have her? -That's fine with me.
- 내가 가져도 될까요? - 좋아요
You didn't even hesitate!
그냥 막 주는 거야?
Yes! Aren't you glad, Orochimaru?
됐다! 너도 기쁘지, 오로치마루?
She can't be serious about that name...
설마 그 이름으로 날 부르진 않겠지?
You're too cute, Orochimaru.
넌 너무 귀여워, 오로치마루
She's sick! I don't wanna live with her!
이 여자는 미쳤어! 같이 살기 싫어
Without Jashin-chan, how am I gonna clean and cook?
사신짱이 없으면 청소와 요리는 어떻게 하지?
-Sorry, I'll take her back. -No!
- 미안해요, 내가 데려갈래요 - 안 돼요!
Now that's just cruel, you can't do that!
그건 너무 잔인해요 그렇겐 못 해요!
If I can't have Orochimaru...
오로치마루를 내가 가질 수 없다면
You must die.
넌 죽어야 해
No way!
절대 안 돼!
Whoops, I missed.
이런, 빗나갔네
It scraped my tail!
내 꼬리를 스쳤어
Sorry I missed, Orochimaru. At least my blades were sharp.
놓쳐서 미안해, 오로치마루 내 칼이 날카롭지?
Does it hurt?
다쳤니?
I love seeing you in pain, suffering. So adorable!
네가 고통받는 게 너무 좋다 정말 사랑스러워!
Time for a celebratory selfie before I finish you.
널 죽이기 전에 축하 셀피를 찍어야 해
Come on, give me a peace sign.
어서 평화의 V 사인을 해야지
I can't... Please forgive me...
못해... 제발 용서해줘
Too cute! So Insta-worthy.
너무 귀여워! 인스타에 올릴만해
-So good, I can't stop! -I'm dying to go home...
- 좋아서 멈출 수가 없어! - 정말 집에 가고 싶다
Oh, it's 5. Work's over.
5시다, 퇴근이야
Gotta go home!
집에 가야 해!
I refuse to work overtime.
난 야근을 거부한다
That meat you bought at the market?
슈퍼에서 산 고기는
It's in the fridge at the station.
냉장고에 넣어뒀어
Don't forget to take it.
찾아가는 거 잊지 마
Later!
또 봐!
I'll see you again soon.
곧 또 보게 될 거야
She thinks you're adorable. What a freak.
네가 사랑스럽다니 이상한 여자다
She was almost as crazy as you, Yurine.
저 여자도 거의 너만큼 돌았어, 유리네
You mentioned something about a boy earlier.
아까 남자애 얘기했던 거
-What was that about? -What?
- 뭐라고 한 거야? - 뭐?
Oh, that was nothing.
아무것도 아니야
I gotta bury that Tsuchinoko as soon as I get home.
집에 가자마자 쓰치노코를 묻어야겠다
Jinbocho happenings!
진보초 사건!
I meant to go to the train station.
기차역으로 가려던 거였는데
I wasn't paying attention, so I entered the wrong door.
딴 데 신경 쓰다 다른 문으로 들어갔다
JINBOCHO STATION
'진보초역'
Put your phone away when you're walking.
걸을 때는 휴대폰을 넣어두세요
Nice howl, Beth.
멋진 울음소리다, 베스
Let me join you.
나와 같이하자
My mother said the air in the human world is polluted.
우리 엄마가 인간 세계 공기는 오염됐다고 하셨어
Feels good.
기분 좋다
What?
뭐지?
-Please die. -I decline.
- 제발 죽어 - 거부한다
I'm doomed!
난 저주받았어!
If I can't just kill her, I thought I'd politely ask!
저 애를 못 죽이니까 그냥 정중하게 부탁하려고 했다고!
You really thought that was gonna work?
넌 그게 통할 거로 생각했니?
Damn it...
젠장...
I'm gonna take a bath.
난 목욕할 거야
Make sure you take one after me.
내가 목욕하고 나오면 너도 꼭 해
Got it.
알겠다
Did you think you were gonna get lucky just now?
넌 지금 운이 좋다고 생각하겠지?
Just wait...
잠시만 기다려라
Check out the Tsuchinoko!
쓰치노코를 확인하죠!
Hot damn.
섹시하다
I was on my knees, begging her to die.
죽어달라고 무릎을 꿇고 빌었어
Why can't she just die for me already?
그냥 날 위해서 죽어주면 안 되는 거야?
She's so stubborn.
고집이 너무 세
Well, I knew it wasn't gonna be that easy.
물론, 그렇게 쉽지 않을 건 알았지
The mountains are so nice.
산이 정말 멋지네요
Why not take a break from the world and free your body and soul in the mountains?
세상에서 빠져나가 산에서 당신의 몸과 영혼을 쉬세요
You call that taking a break?
그게 휴식하는 거라고?
What's the point in climbing when you're gonna descend anyway?
다시 내려올 걸 뭐 하러 거길 올라가?
Because the mountains are there? I don't understand it one bit.
산이 거기 있기 때문이라고? 난 전혀 이해 못 하겠다
But wait, in those suspense dramas, the murder always takes place...
아니지, 서스펜스 드라마에서 살인이 일어나는 곳은 항상
on a mountain!
산이다!
I'M GONNA KILL YOU!
'널 죽여버릴 거다'
STOP! I'M SORRY I STOLE YOUR WIFE.
'하지 마! 네 아내를 뺏어서 미안하다'
TOO LATE!
'너무 늦었다'
YOU WILL REPENT IN HELL!
'지옥에 가서 반성해!'
I NEVER WANTED YOUR WIFE! ALL I WANTED WAS YOU...!
'네 아내를 원한 게 아니야 내가 원한 건 바로 너야!'
I LOVED YOU TOO!
'나도 널 사랑했다!'
Which means mountains are a prime location for murders.
살인 장소로 산이 제일 좋다는 뜻이지
If I can lure Yurine up into the mountains...
유리네를 산으로 유인할 수 있다면
Killing her would be a piece of cake!
죽이는 건 아주 쉬워
That'll be the end of Yurine!
그걸로 유리네는 끝이다
Now, let's visualize this further.
이제 이 작전을 더 자세히 상상해 봐야지
Check out this view, Yurine.
이 경치를 봐, 유리네
Wow, what a stunning sight.
풍광이 정말 대단하다
Hey, there!
야호!
Finally!
드디어 됐다!
I even get to finish her with my signaturedropkick!
내 특기인 드롭킥으로 그 애를 처치한다
EVIL SMILE
'사악한 미소'
How about this scenario?
이런 각본은 어떨까?
This rope bridge sure sways a lot.
이 줄다리는 심하게 흔들린다
Help me, Jashin-chan.
사신짱, 도와줘
Stop!
하지 마!
Yes! Yes!
그래, 그거야!
But, wait, how about this scenario?
아니야, 잠깐 이러면 어때?
It's a bear.
곰이야
We gotta play dead.
우린 죽은 척해야 해
Now.
지금이다
Let's do this.
해볼까?
Cross punch!
크로스 펀치!
I could get a bear to collaborate with me.
곰이 협조하게 만드는 거지
That's an assured victory for me.
그러면 승리는 보장된 거야
I'm so excited, I'm gonna wet myself.
너무 흥분해서 오줌이 나올 것 같다
That was a nice bath.
목욕하니까 좋다
Hey, Yurine. Any plans for tomorrow?
유리네, 내일 무슨 계획이 있니?
Nope.
없어
Then let's go hiking in the mountains.
그럼 우리 산에 놀러 가자
No way.
안 가
Okay.
그래
It seems like this anime mostly take place in Yurine's room.
이 애니의 배경은 대부분 유리네 방인 것 같아
But it does make sense to be here.
하지만 여기인 게 당연하지
Let's switch it up and be in my room for a change.
조금 변화를 주기 위해서 내 방으로 바꾸자
-Thoughts? -I barely feel the difference.
- 어때? - 다른 게 별로 없어
Okay.
그렇네
Then let's give it a more drastic change.
그러면 더 극적인 변화를 줄까?
-How about that? -It's over-the-top!
- 이건 어때? - 너무 심하잖아!
Jashin-chan?
사신짱?
Got it. I'll be right there.
알겠어, 바로 갈게
Okay.
좋아
Oh, yeah, I'll bring her a gift.
그래, 선물도 가져가야겠다
Thank you very much.
대단히 고맙습니다
BEAN DAIFUKU
'팥 다이후쿠'
I hope she'll like it.
이걸 좋아하면 좋겠다
Oh yeah, can't forget to withdraw the money.
참, 돈도 찾아야지
Hello!
안녕!
Jashin-chan? I'm here.
사신짱? 나 왔어
I even got Fresh Moon for you.
너 주려고 '프레시 문'도 사 왔어
Since it's the end of the month, I stopped by the bank too.
월말이라서 은행도 들렀지
Jashin-chan?
사신짱?
Jashin-chan, what's wrong?
사신짱, 왜 그래?
What's... going on...?
무슨... 일이지?
Why...?
왜...?
Jashin-chan...
사신짱
She's dead...
사신짱이 죽었어
She sounded so happy when she called me earlier.
통화할 때는 즐거워하는 것 같았는데
Jashin-chan!
사신짱!
Your reaction!
반응 좋군!
Your face!
표정도 끝내줘!
I peeked through the closet...
옷장에 숨어서 다 봤지
It was priceless! You should've seen it!
정말 대단했어! 너도 봤어야 해
Ouch, I laughed so hard I fell over.
너무 웃다가 떨어졌네
That's just the skin I shed.
저건 내가 벗은 허물이야
Remember? I shed my skin once every few thousand years.
알지? 난 몇천 년마다 허물을 벗잖아
And today was the day.
오늘이 바로 그날이지
So, I thought of this prank and called you.
그래서 장난칠 생각에 네게 전화한 거야
You really thought I died?
정말 내가 죽은 줄 알았니?
Of course not, right?
당연히 안 죽지
Hey, what's wrong?
왜 그러는 거야?
Did you really think that was funny?
넌 이게 정말 웃긴다고 생각하니?
-What? -You just crossed the line.
- 뭐? - 넌 도를 넘었어
You have no idea how devastated I would be if you were gone.
네가 죽으면 내가 얼마나 충격받을지 전혀 모르는 거야
This isn't good...
이건 안 좋은데...
Medusa's in passive-aggressive mode!
메두사가 수동공격적 모드다!
Let me explain.
설명하죠
Medusa gets passive-aggressive when she's mad to the max!
메두사는 극도의 분노 상태일 때 수동공격적 성향을 보입니다
Another phenomenon that happens once every few thousand years...
이건 수천 년에 한 번 일어나는 현상인
Medusa's passive-aggressive mode.
메두사의 수동공격적 모드다
Two rare events aligned with one another.
희귀한 두 사건이 동시에 일어나다니
It's like celebrating Christmas and New Year's at once.
크리스마스와 설날을 동시에 축하하는 것과 같다
Please excuse me now.
난 이만 갈게
I won't be back for a while.
한동안 안 올 거야
She's pissed.
저 애가 화났다
I don't care about you anymore!
이젠 네게 관심 끊을 거야!
I'm never coming back!
다신 인간 세계엔 안 와!
She's not all cutesy like usual.
늘 귀엽던 그 모습이 아니다
Don't leave, Medusa!
가지 마, 메두사!
You know I suffer from nervous gastritis!
네가 이렇게 가면 난 신경성 위염에 걸려
If you leave me like this,
네가 이렇게 떠나면
my tummy will get all messed up,
내 속이 다 뒤틀릴 거야
and I'll worry myself to death!
그리고 걱정하다 죽을 거라고!
I admit, I crossed the line.
내가 심했던 거 인정할게
I'm sorry.
미안해
I didn't think you would get so upset.
네가 그렇게 화낼지 몰랐어
I'm done. Bye.
됐어, 갈게
Wait!
기다려!
Forgive me, Medusa! You're killing me!
용서해줘, 메두사! 이러면 난 죽을 거야!
Medusa...
메두사...
My tummy...
내 배가...
Just kidding. That was payback.
농담이야 네게 복수한 거다
I'll never leave you.
난 절대로 안 떠나
Medusa!
메두사!
You crossed the line!
너무 심했어!
Go easy on those pranks, okay?
앞으로는 심하게 장난치면 안 돼 알았지?
Yeah, of course. I'm sorry!
응, 알았어 미안해!
I'll never do it again.
다시는 안 그럴 거야
There, there.
그래, 그래
I'm home.
나 왔어
Welcome back!
어서 와!
Fresh Moon is so tasty!
프레시 문은 너무 맛있어!
This creamy texture goes so well with coffee.
부드러운 식감이 커피와 잘 어울려
It goes well with tea too. Want some more?
차도 잘 어울려 더 먹을래?
-I'll unwrap it for you. -Thanks!
- 내가 포장을 까줄게 - 고마워!
Lovey-dovey as usual.
여전히 달콤한 분위기군
Say, "Ah."
"아" 해봐
-Yum! -How is it?
- 앙! - 어때?
Delicious!
맛있어!
You got some on your face.
얼굴에 조금 묻었다
Get it off for me.
네가 닦아줘
Dropkick on her! Yeah her! I’ll take you down again!
드롭킥을 날린다! 저 애야! 널 다시 무찌를 거다!
Hate you! Love doesn’t exist in this world
네가 싫어! 이 세상에 사랑이란 없어
Fear the dropkick! An Angel looks for her halo
드롭킥을 겁내라! 천사는 후광을 찾는다
As she starves to death!
굶어 죽어가면서 말이야
It’s a love and hate relationship,
이건 애증 관계야
can’t leave each other alone
서로를 가만히 두지 않지
Like a galaxy-bursting shooting star!
은하에서 터지는 유성처럼
Slowly, slowly, sneak up and DIE!
천천히, 살금살금 몰래 다가가서 죽인다!
Test my heart, don’t stop
내 마음을 떠봐 멈추지 말고
Let’s go! Dream on! No matter human, angel or devil
가자! 꿈꿔! 인간이건 천사건 악마건
We’re a happy family La la la
우리는 행복한 가족이다 랄랄라
Let me say, I love you!!
내가 말할게 난 널 사랑해!
When all is said and done
모든 것이 끝나면
I’m home! Welcome back, it’s hot pot tonight!
나 왔어! 어서 와, 오늘 밤은 스키야키다!
Come, gather everyone! Let’s enjoy this meal!
모두 어서 모여! 이 요리를 즐기자!
For another crazy tomorrow
내일은 또 정신없을 거야
What next? What next? In the end, Wakeup!
뭔데? 또 뭐지? 결국 깨어나!
Insanity and screaming gnaw at peoples' hearts.
광기와 비명이 사람들의 마음을 갉아먹는다
As justice runs rampage, the city is colored with demons' blood.
정의가 광분할 때 도시는 악마의 피로 물들고
The angels are in despair.
천사는 절망한다
Dropkick on My Devil! We'll dive into your heart in the next episode too!
사신짱 드롭킥! 다음 화에서도 여러분 마음에 깊이 뛰어듭니다!